(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T22:29:20.009794",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the show
Cheering loudly is OK
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights during the show
Cheering loudly is OK
アニメにハマって
I got so hooked on anime...
歌いたくなっちゃった
...that I just had to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら
Watching my favorite scenes...
カラオケ歌えるなんて
...while singing karaoke...
尊すぎてツラい！
...is so precious, it hurts!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Let's find the song you want to sing!
JOYSOUND!
ReGLOSS 2nd Album「Snapshot」の
ReGLOSS's 2nd album, \"Snapshot,\"
レコードとカセットテープが、2026年2月25日よりHMV限定で発売決定しましたー！
is coming out on vinyl and cassette, exclusively at HMV on February 25, 2026!
12月17日いっぱいまでにご予約いただくと、
If you pre-order by December 17...
期間限定予約特典としてスマホサイズステッカーをプレゼント！
...you will get a smartphone-sized sticker as a limited-time bonus!
さらに抽選で5名様にサイン入りポスタープレゼント！
Plus, five winners will be drawn to win a signed poster!
HMV、ReGLOSS、レコード、カセットで検索！
Search for \"HMV ReGLOSS Record Cassette\"!
以上、ReGLOSSでした〜！
That's all from ReGLOSS!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
ATTENTION: To all visitors
紙細工の花びらを
The paper flower petals...
ある人は美しいとぼやいた
...someone muttered they were beautiful.
この地球の横顔は
How does the profile of this Earth...
どう見えてる？ キミの世界では
...look to you? In your world...
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down,
失くしそうなモノだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off only the things I seemed to be losing, ah
手のひらで掬い上げようとしたら
When I tried to scoop them up in my palms,
指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
they slipped through the cracks of my fingers and vanished.
「形あるものだけが
"Tangible things aren't...
すべてじゃないけど
...everything, but...
形あるものが
...tangible things are...
どうしても欲しいよ」
...what I want, no matter what."
この世界を
Though changing...
(da-ra-da)
変えることは
...this world...
(la-la-la-la)
きっとできないけど
...is surely impossible...
(da-ra-da)
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
you should be able to change the world inside you.
芽吹いて 咲いて 実って 枯れて
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, and withering,
何ひとつ欠かせないから
because not a single step can be missed,
(da-ra-da-da)
本日は、ReGLOSS 1st Live
Thank you all for coming today...
「Flashpoint」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
...to ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint"!
Reach the top! We are...
はーい
Hi!
いくよー！
Here we go!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます
To ensure you enjoy the live show to the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします
Photography, recording, and the use of recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへおしらせください
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and let a nearby staff member know.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージにも...
Moshing, diving, jumping high, throwing onto the stage...
大丈夫大丈夫！
It's okay, it's okay!
すいませんね！一発収録とかじゃないんでね！
Sorry about that! It's not a one-take recording, you see!
緊張しちゃってごめんなさい、もう一回行きますね
I'm sorry for getting nervous, let me do it one more time.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージにものを投げ込むなど、ほかのみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Moshing, diving, jumping high, throwing objects onto the stage, and any other actions that cause a nuisance to others or disrupt the performance are strictly prohibited. Please follow the rules and have a great time!
また、本公演は映像配信および、写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください！
Also, please note that cameras for video streaming and photography are present in the venue, and the audience seats may be captured. These videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes, so we appreciate your understanding in advance!
ライブのハッシュタグは、「#ReGLOSS1stLive」です！ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
The hashtag for the live stream is "#ReGLOSS1stLive"! Please use the hashtag to build up the excitement!
それでは開演までもう少々
Well then, there is just a little more time until the curtain rises.
盛り上がる準備はできてますかー！
Are you ready to get excited?!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がるー！
Let's all get excited together!
以上、ReGLOSSでした！
That's all from ReGLOSS!
常識蹴っ飛ばして Welcome people
Kick common sense aside, welcome people!
お行儀良くしてちゃ狂っちゃうよ
If we stay well-behaved, we'll go crazy!
どんな視線も釘付け Pretty girl
We'll captivate every gaze, pretty girls!
一人じゃ足りないこの声を
This voice isn't enough on my own,
響かそうよ 痛いくらいに
so let's make it echo to the point of pain!
ピタパタ足音 私のコマンド式
Pitter-patter footsteps, my command style!
一瞬も傍にいられないけれど
Even if I can't be by your side for a single moment,
妙に面白いから
it's strangely interesting,
胸躍る巡り合い
a heart-pounding encounter.
毎日がSpecial day
Every day is a special day.
散々騒いで 楽しんで
Making a lot of noise and having fun,
夜更かしも許して
forgive us for staying up late too.
どんな夢もね 叶うように
So that any dream can come true,
全部冷まさず温めて包み込もう
let's keep them all warm and embrace them.
移ろう色 褪せるように
As the shifting colors seem to fade,
ハラハラ
Fluttering down...
パッと咲くサクラ
Cherry blossoms blooming in a flash
舞い踊ってミッドサマー
dancing through mid-summer.
アルゴリズムの中
Inside the algorithm,
ショートトリップして
taking a short trip
酔いも醒めるまで
until we sober up.
パッと咲くサクラ
Cherry blossoms blooming in a flash
舞い踊ってミッドサマー
dancing through mid-summer.
アルゴリズムの中
Inside the algorithm,
ショートトリップして
taking a short trip
酔いも醒めるまで
until we sober up.
形あるものだけが
Only the things with a shape
すべてじゃないけれど
aren't everything, but
愛おしいよ
they are so dear.
この世界を変えることは
To change this world
きっとできないけど
is surely impossible, but
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
the world inside you can surely be changed.
芽吹いて 咲いて 実って 枯れて...
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, withering,
何ひとつ欠かせないから
because not a single thing can be left out.
最後にキミが笑ってくれれば
If in the end, you will smile for me,
もうそれだけでいい
then that alone is enough.
I'll always be by your side
ReGLOSS
DAYBREAK
Reach the top!
SNAPSHOT
FOCUS
Otonose Kanade
Ichijou Ririka
Juufuutei Raden
Todoroki Hajime
Flashpoint ReGLOSS 1st Live
Ah...
My heartはskip a beat
My heart is skipping a beat
決まったレシピ通り
Following a set recipe,
様変わりしてく正体
My true self is changing completely,
全然悪くないイマジネーション
In this not-so-bad imagination.
日々の憂いは晴れ間を待って
Waiting for a break in the clouds of my daily worries,
悲しみには別れを告げる
I say goodbye to my sadness.
Sweet 曖昧なロジック放り出して
Sweetly tossing aside ambiguous logic,
滲む空 ピンクはバラ色
The bleeding sky turns rose pink.
どれだけ価値を見せようとしても
No matter how much value I try to show,
君がいなければ何の意味もない
It means nothing without you.
擦り傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion without even a scratch,
針の落ちないレコードさ
Like a record where the needle never drops.
浅い纏まりのない追いかけっこに終止符して
Putting an end to this shallow, messy game of chase,
Come on let's go
遮る向かい風にも逆らう
Defying the headwind that tries to block me,
靡かせて
letting it flutter.
飛び乗って to the future
Hop on and head to the future,
フライングしたって alright restart line!!
even if we jump the gun, it's alright, restart line!!
ときめいてしまえば
Once our hearts start pounding,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
in the blink of an eye, the zone of freedom expands.
ひとつひとつ すべてがドラマ
Each and every moment is a drama.
待ち侘びた daybreak restart line!!
The long-awaited daybreak, restart line!!
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A panorama colored in shifting hues,
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
overflowing with a feeling gradation.
始まりのその時が来た
The time for the beginning has come.
nothing is impossible
マヤカシ 誤魔化し 効かない世界
In a world where deception and cover-ups don't work,
この先は まだ誰も知らない 正解
ahead lies the correct answer that no one knows yet.
傍観してるだけじゃ味気ない
Just standing by as a bystander is so dull.
リアルタイムで通じ合って
Let's connect with each other in real-time.
振り子にかける エモーション 後の祭りでも i don't mind
Swinging our emotions like a pendulum, even if it's too late, I don't mind.
大胆不敵な シチュエーション 行けるところまで行ってみたい
In this fearless situation, I want to go as far as we can.
選択肢にない get off on the way
Getting off along the way is not an option.
共に声を鳴らせ
Let's raise our voices together!
素肌を貫くような 真っ整ぐな痛みが伴っても
Even if it comes with a piercing, direct pain,
この仲間たちと最果てまで
with these friends, I'll go to the very end.
keep running to the end
飛び乗って to the future
Hop on and head to the future,
フライングしたって alright restart line!!
even if we jump the gun, it's alright, restart line!!
ときめいてしまえば
Once our hearts start pounding,
瞬く間に広がる開放区
in the blink of an eye, the zone of freedom expands.
ひとつひとつ すべてがドラマ
Each and every moment is a drama.
待ち侘びた daybreak restart line!!
The long-awaited daybreak, restart line!!
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A panorama colored in shifting hues,
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
overflowing with a feeling gradation.
飛び出せ you raise me up
Fly out, you raise me up,
恐れるものはない restart line!!
there is nothing to fear, restart line!!
綺麗な朝焼けが 不透明な明日を照らすよ
A beautiful sunrise will illuminate the uncertain tomorrow.
restart line!!
皆さん、こんにちは！
Hello, everyone!
ReGLOSS 1st Live 「3D Showcase」へようこそお越しくださいました！
Welcome to ReGLOSS 1st Live "3D Showcase"!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
本日はたくさん楽しんでいって、素敵な一夜にいたしましょう！本日は生バンドでお届けいたします！盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's have lots of fun today and make it a wonderful night! We're performing with a live band today! Let's get hyped!
みんな！次の曲は「Easy Breezy」！
Everyone! The next song is "Easy Breezy"!
盛り上がる準備はいいですか！？
Are you ready to get hyped?!
みんなで大きいドキドキしてね！
Everyone, get super excited!
Okey Dokey とっ散らかってお祭り
Okey Dokey, scattered all over, it's a festival!
Easy Breezy 際限なく my favorite
Easy Breezy, boundlessly my favorite!
Okey Dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey Dokey, we want to stay just like this, right?
Easy Breezy おどろうよ everybody
Easy Breezy, let's dance, everybody!
はい始まった 絡まった からかったやつらは どっかいっちゃった
Yes, it started, we got tangled, those who teased us have gone somewhere else.
誰に頼まれたわけでもないのに 止まらねぇ筆 ここでは誰もが王様なのね
Nobody asked us to do this, but the pen won't stop, everyone is a king here, right?
てか長続きする気がしない とかそんな性格でなにが悪い
Honestly, I don't feel like it'll last long, but what's wrong with having that kind of personality?
ただ好きなもんは好き 外野はお黙りキミ無責任
Just because I like what I like, be quiet spectators, you're so irresponsible.
脳みそイマジネーション 見たもん聞いたもん それ全部血になる
Brain imagination, what I saw and heard, all of it becomes my blood.
飛べる飛べ！なめさせとけ 頭ん中もう完成形見えた
We can fly, fly! Let them underestimate us, I can already see the completed form in my head.
頭ん中もう自由自在 心の網目細かくして
Inside my head is already completely free, making the mesh of my heart finer.
最強の世界できちゃってるわな
The ultimate world has already been created, hasn't it?
easy breezy
一張羅パリッと着込んで 戦闘モードなんだこりゃ
Dressing up in our best clothes, what on earth is this combat mode?
どうせやるならめんどくさくなろうぜ なるようになるのさ easy breezy
If we're gonna do it anyway, let's get messy, things will work out, easy breezy!
限界突破！引き寄せるミラクル！
Exceeding our limits! Pulling in a miracle!
みんな！配信もしっかり見えてますよ！次はもっともっとブンブン振っていってね！
Everyone! We can see the livestream clearly too! Next, wave those penlights even more!
Okey Dokey とっ散らかってお祭り
Okey Dokey, scattered all over, it's a festival!
Easy Breezy 際限なく my favorite
Easy Breezy, boundlessly my favorite!
Okey Dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey Dokey, we want to stay just like this, right?
Easy Breezy おどろうよ everybody
Easy Breezy, let's dance, everybody!
見切り発車で進んじまったね
We started off without a clear plan, didn't we?
街の灯りが後ろに消えてく孤独
The loneliness of the city lights fading behind us.
あっという間の stream
The stream ends in the blink of an eye
皆といる空間が extreme
This space with everyone is extreme
量産する掛け替えのない memories
Mass-producing irreplaceable memories
唯一無二掴み取る next dream
A one-of-a-kind next dream to seize
運命共同体
A shared destiny
伝染してゆく喜怒哀楽
Emotions that spread contagiously
分かち合えるエンパシー 共に目指すは
Sharing empathy, together we aim to...
reach the top yeah
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対的 キラーチューン
An absolute, absolute, absolute killer tune
今 は自由気まま水入らずなユニバース
Now it's a carefree, private universe
reload re reload reload シンクロするシナプス
Reload, re-reload, reload, synapses in sync
限界突破惹きつけるミラクル
A miracle that breaks limits and draws you in
okey dokey 史上最高な bv diz
Okey dokey, the greatest bv diz in history
easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
Easy breezy, if we start singing, it's a favorite
okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey dokey, we want to stay like this
easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody!
ReGLOSS 1st LIVE「Flash x Point」へようこそ！
Welcome to ReGLOSS 1st LIVE "Flash x Point"!
ようこそー！
Welcome!
いつもの挨拶から行きましょう！
Let's start with our usual greeting!
ReGLOSS We are...
ReGLOSS!
では早速、自己紹介からしていきたいと思います！
Now, let's get right into our self-introductions!
はい！ 奏からやりたい！
Yes! Kanade wants to go first!
奏から！
Kanade first!
ReGLOSS 1st LIVE「Flash x Point」にお越しいただきありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to ReGLOSS 1st LIVE "Flash x Point"!
かまこーこと音瀬奏です！
I'm Kanade Otoose, also known as Kamakoo!
みんな会えて嬉しいよ！
I'm so happy to see you all!
黄色になってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for turning your lights yellow!
そして！
And next!
可愛いポジティブジーニアス！
The cute positive genius,
莉々華です！ 一条莉々華だよ！
Ririka here! I'm Ichijou Ririka!
やばい、もうみんなの声めっちゃ浴びてる、今！
Oh my gosh, I'm totally bathing in everyone's voices right now!
ありがとう！ 最高だ君たち！そして！
Thank you! You guys are the best! And next!
はい、ReGLOSSのにぎやか仕切り担当、儒烏風亭らでんでございます。本日はどうぞよろしくお願い申し上げます。
Yes, ReGLOSS's lively MC organizer, Juufuutei Raden here. Thank you so much for having me today!
はい、ぷっぷっぷっ、フラットマルチ課長代理、有栖川ペン太！
Yes, pu-pu-pu, Assistant Flat-Multi Manager, Arisugawa Penta!
ちゅ、き、はじめまして！みなさん、こんちくわ！
Chu-ki, nice to meet you! Hello everyone, konchikuwa!
こんちくわー！
Konchikuwa!
紫ありがとう！
Thank you for the purple lights!
ついに始まりました、ReGLOSS 1st LIVE!
It has finally begun, ReGLOSS 1st LIVE!
なんと会場は...
And guess what? The venue is...
満員！
Fully packed!
ありがとう、みんな！
Thank you, everyone!
こんなにたくさんのグロッサーが集まってくれました！
So many GLOSSERS gathered here for us!
すごい、もう最高の景色ですよ！
Amazing, this is the absolute best view!
皆さん本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you all so much.
思い思いのファッションとかもね。
Seeing all of your unique fashion...
『フィーリンググラデーション』のときちょっとテンションが爆上がりしてしまいましたけれども。
My tension went through the roof during "Feeling Gradation"!
本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much!
今日は最後まで思いっきり楽しんでまいりましょう！
Let's enjoy ourselves to the absolute fullest today!
そしてね、会場だけじゃなくて配信もされております！
And also, this is being streamed online as well, not just at the venue!
配信の皆さん、楽しんでますか？
Everyone on the stream, are you having fun?
配信の皆も！
Those on stream too!
いえーい！ コメントも！
Yay! Keep the comments coming!
そしてそて！ 韓国ではライブビューイングが実施されています！
And moreover! A live viewing is being held in Korea!
アニョハセヨ！
Annyeonghaseyo!
라이브 뷰잉을 보고 계시는 여러분, 재밌게 즐기고 계신가요?
Everyone watching the live viewing, are you having fun?
すごい！ 韓国語！
Amazing! Korean!
すごいじゃないよ、当たり前だろ！
What do you mean "amazing"? Of course I can do it!
はい、ということで早速ですが、今立っているこのステージではなく、
Alright! So to start things off, rather than this stage we're standing on...
なんと2階からの登場でございましたが、皆さんびっくりした？どうだった？
we actually appeared from the second floor! Were you all surprised? How was it?
びっくりした！
I was surprised!
オープニングから『フィーリンググラデーション』そして『ばでぃず』と
From the opening, we performed "Feeling Gradation" and "bv diz"...
2曲続けてお披露目させていただきましたが、皆さんいかがでしたか？
two songs in a row. How did you like it, everyone?
どう？どう？
How was it? How was it?
そしてね、皆さんもお気づきかと思いますけども、
And as you've probably noticed already,
今回のライブはバンドメンバーと一緒にお届けしています！
we're performing this live show together with our band members!
いつも聴いているあの曲がどんなアレンジになるのか、お楽しみに！
Look forward to seeing how the songs you always listen to will be arranged!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
はい、今日の感想や心に残った瞬間はハッシュタグ #リグロス_1stLIVE でぜひポストしてください！
Yes, please post your thoughts on today's show and your favorite moments using the hashtag #リグロス_1stLIVE!
みんなの感想、後で我々見に行きますので、めちゃくちゃ楽しみです。
We'll go check out everyone's posts later, so we're really looking forward to it.
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
それではね、早速ではございますが、次の曲にいきましょうか。
Well then, without further ado, shall we move on to the next song?
あ、でも待って、待って！
Oh, but wait, wait!
YouTubeやTikTokで観てくれている皆さん！
Everyone watching on YouTube and TikTok!
ごめんなさい！
We are so sorry!
ここからは有料...
From here on, it's a paid stream...
あ、ちょっとね、無料公開、あ、待って、早い。
Ah, wait, the free streaming... Wait, that's fast.
そう、早いんだけど、無料配信パートはなんとですね、次の曲までとなっております！
Yes, it is, but the free streaming part is actually only up to the next song!
えー！
No way!
えへへ、やだやだー！
Ehehe! "No way! No way!"
まだまだ、一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、概要欄のリンクから見てください！
For everyone who wants to keep getting hyped up together, please check the link in the description!
はい！
Yes!
みなさん！
Everyone!
ライブはね、まだまだ始まったばかりでちゅよ！
The concert has still just begun!
最後までね、一緒に最高の時間を作ろう！
Let's make the absolute best memories together until the very end!
Snowfall 触れるチョーク
Snowfall, touching the chalk,
喧騒とあやまつ ノイズを鳴らす
ringing noises that mistake with the bustle.
Slow-mo, let me show you
おどけてみせる嘘 虚勢的世界 yeah yeah yeah yeah
the lies put on a show in a world of bravado, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If the sky is falling down
If the stars have no shine
真っ新な紙の上 答え滲ませる
On a brand new sheet of paper, letting the answers run,
すべて思うままに
everything just as I please.
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves out the melody of the waves,
Pandora Pandora 夢を掘り in my heart
Pandora, Pandora, tossing dreams up in my heart,
うつろい色あせるように
as they fade and lose color,
Pandora Pandora 秘密のObject
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object.
Choker... Pam pam pam pam pam
Choker, pam-pam-pam-pam-pam,
Better close the bar, Choker
Pam pam pam pam pam
Pam-pam-pam-pam-pam,
Show some secret, Choker
Choker...
1クールのドラマよりも長いFairy tale
A fairy tale longer than a one-season drama,
嘘 偽りなくて This space
with no lies or falsehoods in this space.
さよならした Plastic mind
I've said goodbye to that plastic mind,
この世に表も裏もない
there's no front or back to this world.
いつも違う表情 おぼつかないアイロニー
An always changing expression, an uncertain irony,
1日を抱きしめてたいのに
even though I want to embrace the day...
ひるむ暇はない 上を目指そう
There's no time to flinch, let's aim for the top.
In our world
I might find out how to be kind
忍び合わせて仮初め 朽ちるまで待ちぼうけ
Sneaking together temporarily, waiting in vain until we rot away,
いずれ花になる
eventually we will become flowers.
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves out the melody of the waves,
Pandora Pandora 夢を掘り in my heart
Pandora, Pandora, tossing dreams up in my heart,
うつろい色あせるように
as they fade and lose color,
Pandora Pandora 秘密のObject
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object.
可能性が
Possibilities are...
Thriving in the past
幾重にも重なって 手を繋ぎに 逢いにいこう
overlapping in layers, let's go meet and hold hands,
すりほどいた
as they slip away,
その向かい風
facing that headwind,
今こそ刹那の願い
now is the time for a fleeting wish,
打ち鳴らせ Wake up
strike it aloud, wake up!
そっと手を振るのパス
Gently giving up a pass,
冬枯れの結晶
a winter-withered crystal.
閉ざしてしまいそうな夜だって
Even on nights that seem ready to close in,
この歌声で繋ぎとめてみせるから
I'll show you I can hold on with this singing voice!
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves out the melody of the waves,
Pandora Pandora 夢を掘り in my heart
Pandora, Pandora, tossing dreams up in my heart,
うつろい色あせるように
as they fade and lose color,
Pandora Pandora 秘密のObject
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object.
Choker, Pam pam pam pam pam
Choker, pam-pam-pam-pam-pam,
Better close the bar, Choker
Pam pam pam pam pam
Pam-pam-pam-pam-pam,
Show some secret, Choker...
今日の...
Today's...
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!